<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="whats_new">
        &lt;b&gt;1.2.8b3&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Support for Eink Nook display reintegrated.&lt;br&gt;
        - New auto multicolumn algorithm with some configuration.&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;1.2.8b2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Multi-column output.&lt;br&gt;
        - Close Fav, Lru and so on windows after start reader (configurable).&lt;br&gt;
        - Font size for files and directory names (configurable).&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;1.2.8b1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Fixed invocation dir from favorites and search results, now shown in main window.&lt;br&gt;
        - Fixed search results representation when search from root.&lt;br&gt;
        - User may have now many home folders.&lt;br&gt;
		- User may disable to go up from home folders.&lt;br&gt;
		- Smart configurable Home button with distinct reaction to tap, double tap and long tap introduced.&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;1.2.7&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Preferences Light Theme for Sony reader and mobiles.&lt;br&gt;
        - Application and readers invocation code fixes.&lt;br&gt;
        - Small layout and visual fixes.&lt;br&gt;
    	&lt;b&gt;1.2.6&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Source code and resources reformatted, caused by i18n.&lt;br&gt;
        - Russian translation.&lt;br&gt;
		- WiFi signal strength receive fixed, now with dBm level and "classic" visual output.&lt;br&gt;
		- Application and readers detection and invocation code rewritten, many bugfixes.&lt;br&gt;
		- Fully redesigned to original White NOOK ST "look and feel".&lt;br&gt;
        - Startup as launcher at boot fixes.&lt;br&gt;
        - History supporting fixes.&lt;br&gt;
		&lt;br&gt;    
    	&lt;b&gt;1.2.5&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Source code cleaned, now compiled without warnings.&lt;br&gt;
        - Source code prepared to i18n.&lt;br&gt;
        - Reading Lists (i.e. FAVs, LRUs) with full UTF8 support.&lt;br&gt;
		- Writing Lists (i.e. FAVs, LRUs) now is more frequent.&lt;br&gt;        
		- Added \"Power Off\" functionality (in complement to \"Reboot\") and rewriting implementation.&lt;br&gt;
		&lt;br&gt;    	
    	&lt;b&gt;1.2.4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
    	- Sony PRS-T1 support is added, some layout changes.&lt;br&gt;
    	- Optional return to main window after application starts from \"All Applications\" window.&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;1.2.3&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Context menu items \'Open with ...\' and \'Create intent ...\' added. Note that these items can be disabled via configuration settings.&lt;br&gt;
        - Search root can be comma separated directories list as well as a single directory.
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.2.2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - All configured networks now are present in advanced screen.
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.2.1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
         - New buttons: scroll up/down by big steps. Note that the step length is configurable.&lt;br&gt;
         - New advanced information screen (marked with \'#\' character).
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.2.0&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New directory navigation, visible scrollbar (see settings).&lt;br&gt;
        - gl16 mode (eInk refresh mode) may be set now via settings.
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.1.3&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Check HW and warn if it isn\'t NookSimpleTouch.
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.1.2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Associations settings allows now to configure explicit applications invocation  as well as general intent creation.&lt;br&gt;
        - Obsolete \'how to call readers\' setting removed.
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.1.1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New Cancel/Revert buttons in settings screen.
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.1.0&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Task manager / battery manager - just tap on memory or battery status (bottom of the main screen, launcher mode only).</string>
    
</resources>
