<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="about_help">
        &lt;b>HELP&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        ReLaunch is a versatile reading programs launcher and system-wide shell for Nook Simple Touch (also supported by Sony PRS-T1).&lt;br>
        It is assumed that the user library is organized in an ordered structure
        of folders and files have names of books that match their names.&lt;br>
        ReLaunch supports flexible configuration of many on-screen buttons for quick
        access to certain features of the program and run third party applications.&lt;br>
        Non-obvious possibilities:&lt;br>
        - Some functions of the program available only with run as a desktop shell for system.&lt;br>
        - Some functions require a device with root-access, or only implemented for
        Nook Simple Touch (you will receive appropriate notice).&lt;br>
        - On-screen scrolling buttons support double click to navigate to the specified
        number of percents in list and long-click to quickly move to the end (beginning) of the file list.
        This feature often will not work properly, be careful (you need to enable it in settings).&lt;br>
        - If you open with the button, for example, the second-to-read book, it will be after the opening of the first.
        Thus, you will start in round fashion two (three, etc., depending on the configuration), the last-readed books.&lt;br>
        &lt;br>
    </string>
    <string name="about_appr">
        &lt;b>APPRECIATIONS&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - CoolReader Engine project (Eink support code)&lt;br> 
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://sourceforge.net/projects/crengine/">http://sourceforge.net/projects/crengine/&lt;/a>&lt;br>
        - Interactivemania (icons pack)&lt;br>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.interactivemania.com/">http://www.interactivemania.com/&lt;/a>&lt;br>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.defaulticon.com/">http://www.defaulticon.com/&lt;/a>&lt;br> 
        &lt;br>
        </string>
    <string name="whats_new">
        &lt;b>CHANGELOG&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.7&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - added annotation window for fb2/epub files&lt;br>
        - Back button may be used for folder navigation&lt;br>
        - Start Folder, selected from context menu, replaces the old ones&lt;br>
        - single line output mode for filenames&lt;br>
        - fixed bug, then longpress event fired after doubletap&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.6&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - updated preferences screen for SONY PRS-T1&lt;br>
        - new option \"Add start folder\" in context menu&lt;br>
        - new options for double and long taps on "Favorite applications" button&lt;br>
        - disabled fullscreen mode in Preferences activity&lt;br>
        - fixed bug with symbol # in file names&lt;br>
        - tunable number of columns of All and Favorite applications&lt;br>
		- added new variable %f to book name template&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.5&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - new appearance of preference screen&lt;br>
        - added support for Sony PRS-T1 buttons&lt;br>
        - added new file associations&lt;br>
        - fixed bug with second line of book title disappearance&lt;br>
        - added options for clear Favorites and Last opened lists&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.4&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - showing the book title in two lines&lt;br>
        - database cleanup function implemented&lt;br>
        - added items separator to files list&lt;br>
        - fixed font size for SONY-PRS-T1 in preferences screen&lt;br>
        - fixed rename file from tags with a template with line break&lt;br>
        - fixed sort order in "Show titles" mode&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.3&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - interface is partially adapted for SONY-PRS-T1&lt;br>
        - save/restore settings function implemented&lt;br>
        - show book titles in Favorites and Last recent opened lists&lt;br>
        - a new mechanism of context menu implementation&lt;br>
        - fixed bug with battery status intent reciever&lt;br>
        - fixed bug of incorrect book series sorting&lt;br>
        - fixed some minor bugs&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.2&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - almost fully implemented file operations (create, rename, copy, move file and folders)&lt;br>
        - book title pattern changed&lt;br>
        - added context menu item [Rename from fb2/epub tags]&lt;br>
        - added saving current position in the directory between calls bookreaders&lt;br>
        - fixed sorting in book titles mode&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.1&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Option "Show hidden files" added to preferences&lt;br>
        - Copy/move file functions added to context menu&lt;br>
        - Show book titles functionality implemented for .fb2 and .epub files &lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.3.0&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - source code cleaning and formatting&lt;br>
        - fixed filtering on directories, now not under filtering&lt;br>
        - some fixes in search (strange behavior)&lt;br>
        - quick scroll in "results screens" fixes&lt;br>
        - preferences "save dialog" only after changing something&lt;br>
        - added ability configure icon size&lt;br>
        - added on-screen scroll buttons for preferences&lt;br>
        - added ability to disable (buggy) percentage scroll on Nook&lt;br>
        - added extended functionality to Last Used, Favorites and Settings buttons&lt;br>
        - added Setup WiFi button to advanced screen&lt;br>
        - Advanced, Memory, Battery buttons now configurable&lt;br>
        - Full new icons and some layout changes - in original NOOK look and feel.&lt;br>
        - Scroll by on-screen buttons changed to satisfy Sony users.&lt;br>
        - Lock functionality in Advanced screen.&lt;br>
        - some changes in Home button configuration.&lt;br>
        - simplify buttons on Preferences screen.&lt;br>
        - force screen orientation change (configurable).&lt;br>
        - Some fixes in power adapter show when attached.&lt;br>
        - Configurable File Manager (now implemented deletion only, sorry) menu items (user can disable).&lt;br>
        - Configurable hiding of known (via associations) file extensions (user can enable).&lt;br>
		- Configurable hiding of known (via home dirs) parts of directories names (user can enable).&lt;br>
		- Fixes in context menu creation for empty dir and leaking of mount sdcard broadcast receiver.&lt;br>
		&lt;b>1.2.10&lt;/b>&lt;br>
		- skipped due quick development&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.2.9&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Home icon changed.&lt;br>
        - Spanish translation added.&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.2.8&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Added USB or AC adapter connection information.&lt;br>
        - Redone support for Eink Nook display.&lt;br>
        - Configurable multicolumn output.&lt;br>
        - Close Fav, Lru and so on windows after start reader (configurable).&lt;br>
        - Font size for files and directory names (configurable).&lt;br>
        - User may have now many home folders.&lt;br>
        - User may disable to go up from home folders.&lt;br>
		- Smart configurable Home button with distinct reaction to tap, double tap and long tap introduced.&lt;br>                
        - Fixes: "scroll buttons" sometimes not working; invocation dir from favorites and search results, now shown in main window; search results representation when search from root.&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.2.7&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Preferences Light Theme for Sony reader and mobiles.&lt;br>
        - Application and readers invocation code fixes.&lt;br>
        - Small layout and visual fixes.&lt;br>
    	&lt;b>1.2.6&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Source code and resources reformatted, caused by i18n.&lt;br>
        - Russian translation.&lt;br>
		- WiFi signal strength receive fixed, now with dBm level and "classic" visual output.&lt;br>
		- Application and readers detection and invocation code rewritten, many bugfixes.&lt;br>
		- Fully redesigned to original White NOOK ST "look and feel".&lt;br>
        - Startup as launcher at boot fixes.&lt;br>
        - History supporting fixes.&lt;br>
    	&lt;b>1.2.5&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Source code cleaned, now compiled without warnings.&lt;br>
        - Source code prepared to i18n.&lt;br>
        - Reading Lists (i.e. FAVs, LRUs) with full UTF8 support.&lt;br>
		- Writing Lists (i.e. FAVs, LRUs) now is more frequent.&lt;br>        
		- Added \"Power Off\" functionality (in complement to \"Reboot\") and rewriting implementation.&lt;br>
    	&lt;b>1.2.4&lt;/b>&lt;br>
    	- Sony PRS-T1 support is added, some layout changes.&lt;br>
    	- Optional return to main window after application starts from \"All Applications\" window.&lt;br>
        &lt;b>1.2.3&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Context menu items \'Open with ...\' and \'Create intent ...\' added. Note that these items can be disabled via configuration settings.&lt;br>
        - Search root can be comma separated directories list as well as a single directory.
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.2.2&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - All configured networks now are present in advanced screen.
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.2.1&lt;/b>&lt;br>
         - New buttons: scroll up/down by big steps. Note that the step length is configurable.&lt;br>
         - New advanced information screen (marked with \'#\' character).
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.2.0&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - New directory navigation, visible scrollbar (see settings).&lt;br>
        - gl16 mode (eInk refresh mode) may be set now via settings.
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.1.3&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Check HW and warn if it isn\'t NookSimpleTouch.
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.1.2&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Associations settings allows now to configure explicit applications invocation  as well as general intent creation.&lt;br>
        - Obsolete \'how to call readers\' setting removed.
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.1.1&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - New Cancel/Revert buttons in settings screen.
        &lt;br>&lt;b>1.1.0&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - Task manager / battery manager - just tap on memory or battery status (bottom of the main screen, launcher mode only).
        </string>

</resources>